Finding Aid for the Collection of Heavy Metal Music Material LSC.2269
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of Heavy Metal Music material
1964-2016
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.2269
17.1 linear feet (10 boxes, 5 half boxes, 3 cartons, 1 shoebox, 2 media boxes, 5 flat boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, and 1 map folder)
Collection of published works, archival material, and ephemera related to heavy metal music and fan culture.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Books and DVDs in this collection have been individually cataloged in the UCLA Library online catalog. Records for these items may be found by searching this keyword string, "Collection of heavy metal music material."
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
CONTAINS AUDIO and AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed audio and audiovisual materials. Audio and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access, unless otherwise noted in a Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Purchase from The Book Shop, Covina CA, 2015. Additional purchases and donations from The Book Shop, 2015-2017. Purchase of Jetboy flyers from Boo-Hooray, New York, 2016.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9976325133606533
Biography/History
Heavy metal is a genre of rock music that began to emerge in the late 1960s. Many subgenres fall within metal music, including glam metal, thrash metal, and death metal. In Los Angeles, the Sunset Strip area of West Hollywood was home to a vibrant heavy metal scene, particularly in the 1980s.
Scope and Content
The collection gathers published works, musical recordings, and ephemera related to the heavy metal music genre from the late 1960s through the present. Published works include biographies and autobiographies of musicians, histories of the heavy metal genre, and magazines. The collection also features approximately 600 fliers announcing shows in the Los Angeles and San Francisco areas, along with backstage passes, t-shirts, photographs, and scrapbooks. The Recordings series includes vinyl records, audiocassettes, and compact discs, some of which have been signed by the artists. The collection is also strong in metal-related fanzines from throughout the United States and world.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Books and DVDs
Series 2: Show fliers
Series 3: Photographs, ephemera, and memorabilia
Series 4: Fanzines
Series 5: Magazines
Series 6: Recordings
Rock musicians -- Archives.; Rock music; Heavy metal (Music)
- Series 1: Books and DVDs, 1964-2015
  Scope and Content
  A selection of biographies, autobiographies, and studies of the heavy metal genre are housed in Boxes 1-3, Box 10, Box 11, Box 13 and Box 16. Many of the books are signed, and some are accompanied by related photographs.
  Books and DVDs in this collection have been individually cataloged in the UCLA Library online catalog. Records for these items may be found by searching this keyword string: "Collection of heavy metal music material."
  Organization and Arrangement
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by author within each box.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  COLLECTION CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Cataloged resources, 1964-2015 (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 10, Box 11, Box 13, Box 16, Box 30)
    Box 1.
    Canter, Marc and Jason Porath. Reckless Road: Guns N' Roses and the Making of Appetite for Destruction. N.p.: Shoot Hip Press, 2007. First edition. Signed by Canter on the title page.
    Cooper, Alice and Steven Gaines. Me, Alice: The Autobiography of Alice Cooper. New York, NY: G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1976. First edition.
    Criss, Peter and Larry "Ratso" Sloman. Makeup to Breakup: My Life In and Out of Kiss. New York, NY: Scribner, 2012. First edition, #633 of 1,000 copies signed by Criss as part of a limited edition, with related documentation laid in.
    Echols, Damien. Life After Death. New York, NY: Blue Rider Press, 2012. First edition. Signed by Echols on the half-title.
    Fieldy and Laura Morton. Got the Life: My Journey of Addiction, Faith, Recovery, and Korn. New York, NY: William Morrow, 2009. First edition. Signed and dated by Fieldy on the title page, accompanied by a photograph from the book signing.
    Frehley, Ace and Joe Layden and John Ostrosky. No Regrets: A Rock 'N' Roll Memoir. New York, NY: Gallery Books/MTV Books, 2011. First edition. Signed by Frehley on the title page, accompanied by a photo from the book signing.
    Gore, Tipper. Raising PG Kids in an X-rated Society. Nashville, TN: Abingdon Press, 1987. First edition. Inscribed by Gore on the half-title.
    Mustaine, Dave and Joe Layden. Mustaine: A Heavy Metal Memoir. New York, NY: itbooks, 2010. First edition. Signed by Mustaine on the half-title, accompanied by a photograph from the book signing.
    Nelson, Dan. All Known Metal Bands. San Francisco, CA: McSweeney's, 2008. First edition.
    Osbourne, Ozzy and Chris Ayres. I Am Ozzy. New York, NY: Grand Central Publishing, 2009. First edition. Signed by Osbourne on the half-title, accompanied by a photograph from the book signing.
    Raschke, Carl A. Painted Black: From Drug Killings to Heavy Metal - The Alarming True Story of How Satanism is Terrorizing Our Communities. New York, NY: Harper & Row, 1989. First edition. Signed by Raschke on the half-title.
    Sharp, Ken, Paul Stanley, and Gene Simmons. Nothin' to Lose: The Making of KISS (1972-1975). New York, NY: itbooks, 2013. First edition. Signed by Paul Stanley and Gene Simmons on the half-title, and by Ken Sharp on the following leaf, with a flyer and original photographs from the September 10, 2013 book signing laid in.
    Sherry, James and Neil Aldis. Heavy Metal Thunder: Kick-Ass Cover Art from Kick-Ass Albums. San Francisco, CA: Chronicle Books, 2006.
    Simmons, Gene. Sex Money Kiss. New York, NY: New Millennium Press, 2003. First edition: autographed limited edition, signed by Simmons on the front flyleaf.
    Slash and Anthony Bozza. Slash. New York, NY: HarperCollins, 2007. First edition. Signed by Slash on the title page.
    Snider, Dee. Shut Up and Give Me the Mic: A Twisted Memoir. New York, NY: Gallery Books, 2012. First edition. Signed by Snider on a prefatory blank leaf.
    Stanley, Paul. Face the Music: A Life Exposed. New York, NY: HarperOne, 2014. First edition. Signed by Stanley on the title page.
    Taylor, Corey. Seven Deadly Sins: Settling the Argument Between Born Bad and Damaged Good. Textual photographs. Cambridge, MA: Da Capo Press, 2011. First edition. Signed by Taylor on the title page.
    Wiederhorn, Jon and Katherine Turman. Louder Than Hell: The Definitive Oral History of Metal. New York, NY: itbooks, 2013. First edition. Signed by Wiederhorn, Turman, Scott Ian, and Stephanie Cabral on front flyleaf.
    Box 2.
    Adler, Steven and Lawrence J. Spagnola. My Appetite for Destruction: Sex & Drugs & Guns N' Roses. New York, NY: itbooks, 2010. First edition. Signed by Adler and Spagnola on the title page.
    Bashe, Philip. Heavy Metal Thunder: The Music, Its History, Its Heroes. Foreword by Rob Halford. Garden City, New York, NY: Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1985. First edition.
    Burroughs, William S. Nova Express. New York, NY: Grove Press, Inc., 1964. First edition.
    Chirazi, Steffan ed. So What! The Good, The Mad, and the Ugly. New York, NY: Broadway Books, 2004. First edition.
    Dawes, Laina. What Are You Doing Here? A Black Woman's Life and Liberation in Heavy Metal. Foreword by Skin of Skunk Anansie. Brooklyn, NY: Bazillion Points, 2012. First edition.
    Dunn, Sam, et al. Metal: A Headbanger's Journey. Toronto, ON: E1 Entertainment, 2009. Two-Disc Special Edition, with a mini-documentary on Norwegian Black Metal, extended interviews, and other special features.
    Ellefson, David and Joel McIver. My Life with Deth: Discovering Meaning in a Life of Rock & Roll. Foreword by Alice Cooper. New York, NY: Howard Books, 2013. First edition. Signed by Ellefson on the title, with a flyer from the book signing event laid in.
    Giroux, Annick. Hellbent for Cooking: The Heavy Metal Cookbook. Brooklyn, NY: Bazillion Points, 2009.
    Harrigan, Brian and Malcolm Dome. Encyclopedia Metallica: The Bible of Heavy Metal. London: Bobcat Books, 1980. First edition.
    Heyn, John and Jeff Krulik. Heavy Metal Parking Lot. Videorecording. Portland, OR: Film Baby, 2007.
    Ian, Scott. I'm the Man: The Story of That Guy from Anthrax. Boston, MA: Da Capo Press, 2014.
    Klosterman, Chuck. Fargo Rock City: A Heavy Metal Odyssey in Rural North Dakota. New York, NY: Scribner, 2001. First edition. Signed by Klosterman on the title page.
    Konow, David. Bang Your Head: The Rise and Fall of Heavy Metal. New York, NY: Three Rivers Press, 2002. First edition, a paperback original.
    LeVine, Mark. Heavy Metal Islam: Rock, Resistance, and the Struggle for the Soul of Islam. New York, NY: Three Rivers Press, 2008.
    McKagan, Duff. It's So Easy and Other Lies. 16 pp. photographs, most in color. New York, NY: Touchstone, 2011. First edition. Signed by McKagan on the title page, accompanied by a photograph from the book signing.
    Moses, Alan and Brian Pattison. Glorious Times: A Pictorial of the Death Metal Scene (1984-1991). Introduction by Laurent Ramadier. Buffalo, NY: Glorious Times Publishing, 2009. Revised and expanded edition.
    Moynihan, Michael and Didrik Soderlind. Lords of Chaos: The Bloody Rise of the Satanic Metal Underground. Venice, CA: Feral House, 1998. First edition, third printing.
    The Paradise Lost Trilogy: Collector's Edition. Directed by Joe Berlinger and Bruce Sinofsky. 2012. N.p. DVD. A four-disc DVD set including three documentary films about the West Memphis Three, and a 20-page booklet of photographs from the filmmakers' personal archive.
    Ramsey, William. Abomination: Devil Worship and Deception in the West Memphis Three Murders. Lexington, KY: William Ramsey, 2012.
    Wallach, Jeremy, Harris M. Berger, and Paul D. Greene ed. Metal Rules the Globe: Heavy Metal Music Around the World. Durham: Duke University Press, 2011.
    Walser, Robert. Running with the Devil: Power, Gender, and Madness in Heavy Metal Music. Middletown, CT: Wesleyan University Press, 1993.
    Weinstein, Deena. Heavy Metal: A Cultural Sociology. Textual photographs and illustrations. New York, NY: Lexington Books, 1991. First edition.
    Box 3.
    Hammett, Kirk and Steffan Chirazi. Too Much Horror Business: The Kirk Hammett Collection. New York, NY: Abrams, 2013. First edition.
    Oimen, Harald and Brian Lew. Murder in the Front Row: Shots from the Bay Area Thrash Metal Epicenter. N.p.: Bazillion Points, 2011. Author inscribed on free endpaper.
    Patterson, Dayal. Black Metal: Evolution of the Cult. Numerous textual photographs and illustrations, including several in color. Port Townsend, WA: Feral House, 2013. First edition.
    Patterson, Dayal. Black Metal: The Cult Never Dies Vol. 1. N.p.: Decible Books, 2015. Number 132 of 1000.
    Pines, Mark ed. Alice Cooper. New York, NY: Alosco & McLaughlin Enterprises Inc., [1973?].
    Popoff, Martin. Run for Cover: The Art of Derek Riggs. N.p.: Aardvark Publishing, 2006. First edition, #1483 of 1500 trade copies. Signed by Derek Riggs on the front endpaper.
    Box 10.
    Kugelberg, Johan ed. True Norwegian Black Metal: We Turn in the Night Consumed by Fire. Photography by Peter Beste. Introduction by Jon "Metalion" Kristiansen. Brooklyn, NY: Vice Books, 2008. Second edition, limited to 2,500 copies. Signed by Beste on the title page, with a flyer from the book signing event laid in. Accompanied by a promotional poster.
    Box 11.
    Taylor, Matt. Metallica: Back to the Front: A Fully Authorized Visual History of the Master of Puppets Album and Tour. San Rafael, CA: Insight Editions in association with Moonrise Media, 2016.
    Box 13.
    Araya, Jeanette. Bloodline: The Araya Story. Bloomington, IN: Archway Pub., 2015.
    Blythe, D. Randall. Dark Days: A Memoir. Boston, MA: Da Capo Press, a member of the Perseus Books Group, 2015. Signed by Blythe.
    Crockett, Alexandra. Metal Cats. New York, NY: powerHouse Books, 2014. Inscribed by author on back cover.
    Ferris, D. X. Reign in Blood: 33 1/3. New York, NY: Bloomsbury, 2013.
    Fischer, Tom Gabriel. Are You Morbid? Into the Pandemonium of Celtic Frost. London: Sanctuary Publishing Limited, 2000.
    Herron-Wheeler, Addison. Wicked Woman: Women in Metal from the 1960s to Now. N.p.: Addison Herron-Wheeler, 2014.
    Mudrian, Albert. Choosing Death: The Improbable History of Death Metal & Grindcore. Los Angeles, CA: Feral House, 2004.
    Mudrian, Albert. Choosing Death: The Improbable History of Death Metal & Grindcore. Philadelphia, PA: dB Books, 2015.
    Rudolph, Mark, ed. Morbid Tales!: A Tribute to Celtic Frost. Michigan, IN: CV Comics in cooperation with Corpse Flower Records, 2014.
    Trilling, Roger, ed. The Wild Palms Reader. New York, NY: St. Martin's Press, 1993.
    Inside Metal: Pioneers of L.A. Hard Rock and Metal. Directed by Bob Nalbandian. 2014. N.p.: DRK Productions. DVD.
    Inside Metal: Pioneers of L.A. Hard Rock and Metal II. Directed by Bob Nalbandian. 2015. N.p.: Metalrock. DVD.
    The Distorted Island: Heavy Metal Music and Community in Puerto Rico. Directed by Osvaldo González-Sepúlveda. 2015. N.p. DVD.
    Box 16.
    Christe, Ian. Everybody Wants Some: The Van Halen Saga. Hoboken, NJ: John Wiley & Sons, 2007.
    Gritter, Headley. Rock 'N' Roll Asylum: Conversations with the Madmen of Music. New York, NY: Delilah Books, distributed by the Putnam Publishing Group, 1984.
    Lee, Tommy and Anthony Bozza. Tommy Land. New York, NY: Atria Books, 2004.
    Luce, Ed. Wuvable Oaf. Seattle, WA: Fantagraphics Books, 2015. "What the fuzz" Special Edition, in sleeve.
    Osbourne, Sharon. Extreme: My Autobiography. New York, NY: Springboard Press, 2005.
    Renoff, Greg. Van Halen Rising: How a Southern California Backyard Party Band Saved Heavy Metal. Toronto, ON: ECW press, 2015.
    Sixx, Nikki. The Heroin Diaries: A Year in the Life of a Shattered Rock Star. New York, NY: Pocket Books, 2007.
    Snider, Dee and Philip Bash. Dee Snider's Teenage Survival Guide: How to Be a Legend in Your Own Lunchtime. Garden City, NY: Dolphin Books, Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1987.
    Stubberud, Jorn "Necrobutcher." The Death Archives: Mayhem 1984-94. N.p.: Ecstatic Peace Library, 2016.
    Wall, Mick. W.A.R.: The Unauthorized Biography of William Axl Rose. New York, NY: St. Martin's Press, 2007. First American edition.
    Welch, Brian "Head." Save Me from Myself: How I Found God, Quit Korn, Kicked Drugs, and Lived to Tell My Story. New York, NY: Harpercollins, 2007.
    Box 30.
    Neely, Tom and Igloo Tornado. Henry and Glenn Forever and Ever. Portland, OR: Mircrocosm Publishing, 2017.
    Slagel, Brian and Mark Eglinton. For the Sake of Heaviness: The History of Metal Blade Records. New York, NY: BMG, 2017.
    Box 30: For the Sake of Heaviness: The History of Metal Blade Records contains one audiocassette.
    - Heavy Metal Parking Lot, 1986; yrlsc_2269_002_001; Heyn, John; Krulik, Jeff; Pirate Video; 1 video recordings (1 DVD; Duration 0:16:40) (Box 2, Case 1)
      CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
- Series 2: Show fliers, circa 1980-2016
  Show and event fliers from metal concerts, festivals, and parties, primarily from Los Angeles and San Francisco areas. The bulk of fliers date from the 1980s and 1990s.
  Materials are arranged geographically.
  - Show Flyers, Northern and Southern California, circa 1980-2000; Fliers range in size from 5 x 7 inches to 16.5 x 11 inches, with most 8.5 x 11. Some with remnants of masking tape. (Box 4, Folder 1-12)
    Approximately 600 fliers and handbills promoting San Francisco and Los Angeles-area heavy metal venues and bands. Groups such as Poison, Faster Pussycat, The Lovedolls, Saint Vitus, LA Guns, Taz, Metallica, Slayer, Blind Illusion, Leathur Panteez, Death Angel, Flotsam & Jetsam, Wendy O. Williams, Body Count, Armored Saint, and Primus are represented. Featured venues include the Troubadour, the Roxy Theatre, Gazzarri's, XPoseur54, Chuck Landis' Country Club, The Stone, The Omni, and Mabuhay Gardens.
  - Clash of the Titans show flier featuring Anthrax, Megadeth, Slayer, and Alice in Chains., 1991 June 3 (Box 10)
  - Fliers, Los Angeles and area, 1983-1991 (Box 17, Folder 1-2, Box 24, Box 23, Folder 2)
    Provenance/Source of Acquisition
    Purchase: Boo-Hooray, May 2016.
    Fliers, handbills, and ephemera from Los Angeles-area heavy metal shows. Includes bands such as Damn Yankees, Doll, Faster Pussycat, Funhouse, Great White, L. A. Guns, Loudness, Yngwie Malmsteen, Motorcycle Boy, Poison, Salty Dog, Warrant, and the Zeros. Featured venues include Gazzari's, Chuck Landis' Country Club, the Troubadour, the Roxy, and the Whisky-a-Go-Go.
  - Club fliers, 1980s (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Show and event fliers, 1987-2016 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Series 3: Photographs, ephemera, and memorabilia, 1970-2015
  Materials include photographs, scrapbooks, concert programs, fan club letters, backstage passes, set lists, posters, and other ephemera. Also includes concert t-shirts and battle vests made by fans.
  Materials are arranged alphabetically.
  - Battle vest personal statement, 2014 April 17 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Two page narrative by Armando Rollice of East Los Angeles, CA, describing how he assembled his denim vest featuring patches, metal studs, and pins, and how much he loves heavy metal music.
  - Battle vest, circa 2012-2014 (Box 28)
    Levi Strauss denim vest featuring 24 patches sewn on by Armando Rollice. Bands represented include Motorhead, Slayer, Celtic Frost, Venom, Saxon, Iron Maiden and Overkill. Vest is decorated with metal studs, a few small buttons, and safety pins.
  - Battle vest, circa 1980-82 (Box 28)
    Lee Cooper denim vest with Rush, Black Sabbath, Motorhead, and Rainbow pins, and three hand-sewn patches representing AC/DC, Black Sabbath, and Iron Maiden.
  - Alice Cooper t-shirt, 1987 (Box 9)
    Red t-shirt, size medium, silkscreen printed on front and back, from Alice Cooper's The Nightmare Returns tour. Signed and dated by Alice Cooper just below the right shoulder.
  - Animal Bag photographs and negatives, 1980s-1990s (Box 10, Box 5, Folder 2)
    Photographs taken by Drake Zabriskie in Glendale, CA circa 1990. Box 5, Folder 2 contains 61 negatives and 4 8" x 10" prints. Box 10 contains a 10" x 15" black and white photograph.
  - Anthrax tour schedule, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Custodial History
    From the personal collection of journalist and author, Lonn Friend.
    Tour book for Anthrax's January 1992 European tour co-headlined with Public Enemy. Includes the band's complete itinerary and travel schedule. Signed by Scott Ian on the front panel.
  - Anthrax playing cards, undated (Box 12)
  - Bad Influence photos and flyers, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Black Sabbath world tour program, 1976-77 (Box 10)
  - Britny Fox fan club letter, May 9, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cannibal corpse poster, December 19, 1992; Offset printed on a sheet of white stock, 22.5" x 34". (Box 25)
    Poster promoting a concert headlined by Cannibal Corpse, and also featuring Cenotaph and Blackthorn at the Auditorio Lomas Verdes in Naucalpan, Mexico. Inscribed by Cannibal Corpse vocalist Chris Barnes on the band's photograph.
  - Cathouse club letters, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Newsletters about events at this Los Angeles club, and flyers for performances.
  - Frankii Elliott publicity photo with note, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Faster Pussycat autographs, undated; Signatures in red marker on La Quinta Royale Motor Inn, Corpus Christi, Texas stationery. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Girlschool programs, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Concert program from Girlschool's Hit and Run Tour. Signed on the front panel by Kim McAuliffe, Enid Williams, Denise Dufort, and Kelly Johnson.
  - GWAR flyers, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Jetboy flyers and fan club letters, 1985-1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Fan club newsletters, album promotion flyers, and show announcement flyers mostly for Los Angeles area clubs.
  - L. A. Guns memorabilia: backstage passes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    From the personal collection of Tracii Guns.
  - L. A. Guns memorabilia: t-shirt from No Mercy Tour, 1988 (Box 9)
  - L. A. Guns memorabilia: Gold Record, 1988 (Box 24)
    Framed RIAA gold record commemorating the sale of more than 500,000 copies of L.A. Guns' self-titled debut album, presented by Tracii Guns to his father Rick Ulrich.
  - L. A. Guns memorabilia: poster, 1985; 23" x 35" offset lithographic, printed in black on a white background. (Box 25)
    Poster issued by Raz Records (a fake independent label, named after the band's manager, Raz Cue) in conjunction with the release of the band's debut EP, Collector's Edition No. 1 (1985). Offset lithographic, printed in black on a white background. Signed by guitarist Tracii Guns in the lower right corner.
  - Lamb of God set list, November 5, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    From concert at Piere's Entertainment Center, Ft. Wayne, Indiana.
  - Metallica scrapbook, 1990s (Box 22)
    Compiled by a fan. Mostly magazine clippings.
  - Motley Crue world tour program, 1989-90 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Motorhead scrapbook, 1980, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
    Scrapbook of clippings, Motorheadbangers fan club correspondence, and other material assembled by a British fan named Andy, around 1980. Includes an introductory form letter from early 1980, merchandise order forms, and a list of Motorhead's U.K. Autumn Tour 1980 dates, which also mentions the recording of their new album Ace of Spades (1981). Among the clippings are the "Fallout Favourites" column from Flexipop magazine, a full page ad for the album Overkill (1979), and a review of Motorhead's 1980 concert at Bingley Hall in Stafford with Saxon and Girlschool. Accompanied by two later issues of the Motorheadbangers newsletter (September/October 1988 and August 1989), a pictorial discography issued by Motorheadbangers in 1988, and a flyer for the Motorheadbangers 10th Anniversary Party at the Hippodrome on June 7, 1989, which included a special appearance by Motorhead.
  - Music in Action petition, 1987 (Box 10)
    Published petition condemning the PMRC and DecencyInMedia, clipped from an issue of Billboard magazine.
  - Quiet Riot "Metal Health" European tour scarf, 1984 (Box 9)
    Black synthetic fiber scarf with red lettering and green fringe. Features images of Rudy Sarzo, Carlos Cavazo, Frankie Banali, and Kevin DuBrow.
  - Quiet Riot production booklet for "20 Years of Metal Health" concert video shoot, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Binder of production information including set list, stage setup, schedule, release forms, and crew and vendor lists for concert filmed at The Key Club in Los Angeles, September 26, 2002.
  - Ratt concert program, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)